▍2026 辛辛那提 WTA1000 第三轮
萨巴伦卡 6-1 6-3 王欣瑜 · 赛后场上采访
to 61 63 comfortable and dominant.
六比一 六比三 轻松又强势
Arena Sabalanka sailing
萨巴伦卡一路
through to the fourth round in Cincinnati.
闯进辛辛那提第四轮
She has an incredible record
她在这里的战绩
at this tournament.
相当惊人
She is a former champion
她是这里的前冠军
and that was a comfortable night's work
今晚的胜利很轻松
for the world number one.
对这位世界第一来说
61 63 Look at the smile on your face.
看看你脸上这笑容
You must be pleased
你一定很满意
with your performance tonight.
今晚的表现吧
Especially you played her a few years ago.
尤其是你几年前跟她打过
It was a tough three setter,
那次打了艰难的三盘
but tonight very different.
今晚完全不一样
Well, yeah, I cannot complain.
是啊 没什么好抱怨的
She's a tough opponent and to get this win
她是个难缠的对手 能拿下这场
in straight sets and under like what,
而且直落两盘 用时还不到
an hour, it's it's insane result.
一个小时 这个结果太疯狂了
I'm super happy to be through.
能晋级我特别开心
What do you think made you
你觉得是什么让你
so dangerous tonight?
今晚这么难对付？
I mean, you were hitting the ball deep.
我是说 你把球打得很深
You never let her get into a rhythm at all.
完全没让她找到节奏
What are you most pleased with?
你对哪一点最满意？
I don't know. I think I really trusted myself.
不知道 我很相信自己
I was just going for my shots
我就是放手去打
without like overthinking.
没有想太多
And I think that was the the the weapon
我觉得那就是今晚
of tonight match.
这场球的武器
And I'm super happy I was able
我也很高兴自己能
to stay focused and to be, you know,
保持专注 就是那种
in every point.
每一分都在状态里
That's 45 consecutive wins
这是连续四十五场
at 1,00 tournaments.
在一千分赛的胜利
You're the leader of active players
你是现役球员里
on the WTA.
排在第一位的
That says a lot about what you
这说明了很多
do to your game when you're at a 1000,
打一千分赛时你的状态
when you're at a major.
打大满贯时也是
What is it about these events?
这些赛事有什么特别？
I'm wondering if it has anything
我在想这是不是
to do with the fans here in Mason, Ohio.
和梅森这里的球迷有关
But
不过
I mean, of course, guys, I'm super happy
我是说 当然 各位 我特别开心
to be back and to play in front of you all.
能回来在你们面前打球
It's it's always super enjoyable.
一直都特别享受
Thank you for coming.
谢谢你们来
Thank you for supporting you guys.
谢谢你们一直支持
Make this place very very special.
让这里变得特别不一样
Thank you.
谢谢
Okay, your 2024 champion everybody
好的 各位 你们的 2024 年冠军
is through to the round of 16.
已经晋级第四轮
Arena Sabalena.
萨巴伦卡